Why do these days pile up
kasanete kita hibi ga
Only to come crashing back down?
kuzure ochita no wa naze da
This never-ending flow of time
tomaranai jikan wa
Continues to wear our souls away
itsu datte bokura wo kowashite iku
With this stifled voice of mine
oshikoroshita koe wo
I wait for the dusk to fade
nagetsukeru yoru wo mate
But I know that tomorrow will certainly come
yuzurenai asu wo iku dakedo
I won't let anyone else choose my fate
mou dare ni mo jama ha sasenai
I don't care what awaits me on the other side
dou natta tte ii to omoeru
All I know is to embrace this moment and live on
shunkan dake wo kakaete ikiro