Yes.
I found it.
He's on the phone again.
Is it Mr. Hanekoma?
Thanks.
--I'm counting on you, Mr. Hanekoma.
You really know Shibuya.
--Why would he work with
someone like Joshua?
--I'm counting on you, Mr. Hanekoma.
You really know Shibuya.
Does Mr. Hanekoma know
that this guy killed me?
Hi there, Neku.
Sweet dreams?
The worst.
How can you act so casual?!
Well, we are partners.
If you erased me, you'd be done for too.
The Reapers' Game and
missions don't matter to you.
You're just out for yourself!
Because unlike me, you're alive!
That's not true, Neku.
It is true! You won't get erased!
A mission?!
"Beat the bosses of 2.2360679's 0 and 5.
You have 60 minutes."
I'm playing by the same rules
as the rest of you.
If I'm erased in the Underground,
I'll be erased in the Realground too.
What?
You came to the Underground
even though you might die?
It beats being in the Realground.
So, Minamimoto was behind the Taboo Noise?
This is a serious act of treason.
I'll discuss Minamimoto's
punishment with the Composer.
I request a swift resolution.
By the way,
a second-time Player, Neku Sakuraba,
is proving exceptionally long-lived.
What do you think of that , sir?
So, that's how it is.
The composer has a mischievous streak.
The bosses of 0 and 5...
What's 2.2360679?
Some kind of code?
I've got a guess.
I hope this hits.
OK, Neku, let's keep going.
I thought so. Only Route 5 is open today.
How'd you know?
2.2360679 is the square root of 5.
There's even a mnemonic for it.
Damn it! He's screwing with us.
Route 5 runs starts at Scramble Crossing
and runs through Center Street, AMX,
Tipsy Tose Hall, Tokyu Hands, and Udagawa.
Then the bosses of 0+5...
...are in Scramble Crossing and...
One, two...
Udagawa!
You got it.
We just beat the first boss,
so if we beat the boss of Udagawa,
we clear the mission.
Damn it!
There's a lot of tough Noise today!
Broadly speaking,
there are two types of Noise.
Stray Noise is the natural product of
negative human emotion in the Realground.
Stray Noise obeys Reapers
and attacks Players.
And these are the other type?!
That Reaper, Kariya,
called them Taboo Noise.
They attack Players and Reapers
regardless of missions.
I can't afford to lose!
We did it, Nao!
Nao! Nao!
Looks like I've had it.
Sorry, So--
Nao!
Nao's gone.
God damn it!
Sorry.
You guys...
If we'd gotten here a little sooner...
H-Hey!
Stick it out to the end.
Get back the partner
they made your entry fee.
You've gotta come back... to life.
Shit!
Again. Before my eyes.
But we're still alive.
What's happens to the ones who aren't?!
I know we Players are
strangers to each other.
And not just Players. Everyone on
the street's a stranger too.
They all have different values
and ways of thinking.
But I...
I met a lot of people
in Shibuya, and I felt it.
I felt my world grow, just a little.
So, I don't want to just shut them out!
That's not like you, Neku,
but it's because you interacted with
others than you can find a new you.
Is that the gist of it?
Let's hurry.
We'll have to clear the mission ourselves.
Uzuki!
You OK?
There's too many of them.
The Game Master must be
mass producing them.
Those two!
What shall we do, Neku?
I don't want to watch someone die.
We'll back them up!
That just leaves these guys!
--OK!
--Hey!
What do you think you're doing?!
What? You'd rather we didn't save you?
We're Reapers! Your enemies, remember?
Anyway, I can take care of my--
Whoa there.
Don't overdo it.
Thanks. You saved us.
Hey! What are you talking about?!
Can't forget to say thanks.
Players saving Reapers?! What a pain!
Let's go, Kariya!
The Game Master's not
gonna play by the rules.
This won't be like last time. Watch out.
How's the time?
Thirty minutes left.
That's plenty.
That's the boss.
Be careful, Neku!
Got it. Let's go!
Fighting up close is risky! Get back!
Another one.
Huh?
Watch out!
Wow. It's surprisingly nimble.
Bye-bye!
Mission clear, huh?
One more day.
Hang on, Shiki.
This is zetta thrilling.
What do you want today?
You guys getting erased
would throw off my plans.
Tomorrow's day seven.
They special day I get
to take you on myself.
Now, time for a question.
How fast am I gonna erase you two?
No clue.
299,729,458 m/s.
Would that be the speed of light?
I'm gonna solve the calculation
I screwed up here that day!
It's finally the last day.
My second Reapers' Game ends today.
That's right.
That hurts.
Promise me.
After today's mission,
I'll make you tell me everything.
I suppose.
"Defeat the Game Master at Mark City.
Incompletes will be erased," huh?
It's a good spot for a base.
Why's that?
All the emotion in Shibuya collects here.
It crashes into Mark City
and shoots up into the sky.
That emotion flows back down
and keeps building up here.
If we can beat him,
it'll all be over.
Hold on, Shiki.
This looks like the only way in.
It's too dark to see clearly.
Watch your step. I wouldn't
want my partner getting hurt.
Mind your own business.
Get your head in the game!
Noise!
Damn it!
It's so dark, I can't tell
where they're attacking from!
I can't get close!
The lights...
There!
Today's the day I take you down!
I switched on the emergency lights.
That makes us even for before.
Good grief. How awkward can Skater Boy be?
Is his "special op" for Mr. Kitaniji
to pretend to pick fights
and protect those boys
from Noise and Reapers?
I've got no clue what's
even right anymore.
What's going on?!
Isn't this weird?!
Space is warping!
It might be the imaginary number plane.
The imaginary what now?
A parallel world an infinitesimal distance
from the one Noise inhabits.
That might be where we're fighting.
Dodge, Beat!
It might be risky to stay too long.
Here.
You dropped this.
I owe you one.
Again?!
Did Minamimoto do this?
This is his base, after all.
We can't get careless.
What're you guys doing here?!
Could it be an inverse matrix?!
A what?
Forget it. You saved me a trip.
But I was hoping to set up the same
situation in the same place as that time.
"That time"?
Yes, that time.
Neku?
So, you killed me,
Minamimoto!
Come and get it!
I'm gonna eliminate you
from my spatial coordinates!
Drown in the sea... of imaginary numbers!
Look, Neku!
Taboo Noise!
And so many of them!
He's been using the Shibuya's emotional
energy that pools at Mark City
to manufacture Taboo Noise.
Be careful!
Right back at you.
What?!
Tera slow!
Neku!
You're zetta slow!
Get down!
This is nothing!
Don't get cocky!
He's way stronger than
everything else so far.
I'm on another level!
This is bad.
We're just getting started.
I've never gotten so much
power from this guy before.
With this, we can win!
I'll draw him out.
You're zetta tough.
You might be the one who gets erased.
What?
Did you know?!
The world's made of numbers!
I've been reverse-engineering
my desired solution all this time!
And this...
...is my answer!
This is...!
What the...?
You can't afford to lose, right, Neku?
You'll survive and make
your wish come true.
Why?
Why did you cover for me?
I always suspected you, so why did you...?
Joshua!
You're...
Congratulations.
You did well to survive again,
and thank you for cooperating with us.
I don't remember helping you.
You dealt with the rebel.
I sent the final mission myself.
Minamimoto unleashed Taboo Noise and
killed many Reapers. You dealt with him.
Thank you.
You used us?
I'm sorry about your partner.
I never expected him to shield you.
Is Joshua...?
He was erased along
with Minamimoto, as you saw.
I haven't apologized yet.
I haven't apologized to him, to Joshua.
He was my partner, but I could
never bring myself to trust him.
I'm the worst.
No need to grieve.
He committed a serious offense.
You mean being alive?
And he gave you your next ordeal.
As his partner, you share his
guilt for breaking the rules.
You will be erased.
But considering the extent
of your service to us,
I will permit you to enter a third game,
albeit with a penalty.
You cannot refuse.
And Shiki? What about Shiki?
Your penalty is disqualification
from all future games.
As far as you're concerned,
the next game is the last.
The next game is the last?
Now, as for your third entry fee...
Here I go again.
This is...
...my last game.
Next time: "Emergency Call."