Day four of the Reapers' Game, huh.
Will anything change if we survive this game?
I have no idea if anything will change,
but I don't want to give up.
On what?
My dream.
Shibuya's so diverse. You see all walks of life here.
I hate Shibuya.
Everyone's wrapped up in themselves, making a racket.
Just like Noise.
Yo! This is where you guys were hangin', huh?
The walls over by Ten-Four are gone today!
Beat! Rhyme!
Everywhere else is blocked, though.
Anyways whatcha guys up to?
Seems like you two are homies now.
We are not.
We were people-watching.
Oh. That scanning shit freaks me out, y'know?
Like, there's so many people out there,  all thinking different things.
Yeah.
And everyone's values are colliding at crazy speeds.
But y'know? Even though Shibuya's this crowded,  nobody notices us.
Yeah.
It makes me feel kinda lonely.
That so?
In the Underground,
I don't have to worry about others noticing me.
Or about people trying to talk to me, either.
I'm fine with not having to talk to anyone.
Y'know, you jus' said some real depressin' shit.
You good?
Yeah. Nothing good will come out of talking to strangers.
I can tell what someone's thinking just by scanning them. It's convenient.
There's something... lonely about that.
I think that you should understand others by listening to what they have to say, though.
You think?
Yeah.
Your stuffed animal's adorable.
You mean Mr. Mew?
Mr. Mew?
Yeah. I made him.
Wanna touch him?
Yeah!
Wow!
Mmm! He's so soft and fluffy!
You're incredible, Shiki!
I made this outfit, too.
Huh?
I'm impressed.
Word.
My dream is to become a fashion designer.
That's a great dream.
I'm jealous. I don't really know what it's like to have a dream.
You "don't know"? Doesn't that just mean that you don't have one?
Hey, Phones!
Watch your temper, Beat!
Listen, Rhyme. You'll find a dream somewhere along the way if you just keep movin' forward.
So, it don't matter if you ain't got one now.
I'm gonna be the best skateboarder in the world!
Yeah!
Someday, I'll find a dream of my own.
Isn't that pendant really rare?
I lined up for it with friends, but I couldn't get one.
It was a birthday present from my big brother.
Wow. You've got a great brother.
Yup!
He's super nice.
I'm really proud of him.
I hear there's an event at Ten-Four!
What?
Hey, hear that?
Let's go!
Hey, what's got everybody so worked up all of a sudden?
They're heading toward Ten-Four.
Well, there's no mission yet, so... Wanna check it out?
If it ain't a mission, I ain't interested.
Oh, wait up, Beat!
Sorry. See you later.
There they go.
What about you, Neku?
I'll go if you want to.
Whoa! What's with this crowd?!
This is normal for Ten-Four.
Oh! They've got new outfits in!
Wow! These are totally cute.
Hey, Eri, what do you...?
Eri?
Sorry.
I used to come here a lot with friends.
What the—?!
Oji!
Eiji!
Who the hell's that guy?
That's Eiji Oji.
He's really taken off recently thanks to his don't-give-a-damn attitude.
Keep it down.
All he did was drink water, right?!
They say, "The Prince sells."
Everything Eiji Oji compliments sells out in no time.
He even pushed that pendant Rhyme had on his blog.
The one you said you waited in line for, right?
The truth is, I'm a bit of a fan.
When it comes to fashion, his comments are spot-on.
That reminds me, you said that you made your own clothes, right?
I thought that they were store-bought.
I only did the sewing. The designs are Eri's.
I want to make clothes for a living.
I want lots of people to wear our clothes.
And I want them to make people happy.
That so?
Yup!
Hey, mind if I take another look at that shop we passed by?
Go for it.
Is that why you're trying so hard?
Does that mean that if you survive these seven days,
your dream will come true?
"Free Spain Hill from the Noise"?
Enough is enough!
They keep coming!
Maybe someone is attracting the Noise here.
Neku! Those two!
Ai, are you mad?
I told you I'm not.
Liar! You're totally mad!
Why would I lie to you?!
—I'm telling you, I'm not mad! —So many Noise!
How do you let things get that bad?
Looks like those two are the cause this time.
No matter how many we erase, more Noise keeps appearing.
I'll figure something out.
Neku, can you take out the Noise around them for me?
Sure! I'm on it!
Get down!
Why are they fighting like this?
I can't believe she's hiding it.
I know that Mina was meeting with Makoto.
Not good. I'm pretty sure Ai's got the wrong idea.
Trying to surprise her might've backfired.
Okay, I'm going to use Imprinting.
What's that?!
It means using your Player pin to speak directly to people's minds.
Please, talk to each other and work this out.
I know about how you and Makoto have been meeting up in private!
You caught on? That figures.
How can you act so calm when—?
Here you go.
What're these?
Don't change the subject!
You two wanted go, right? To 777's concert.
What?
You've always wanted to go, right?
You see, Makoto and I were thinking up a surprise for your birthday.
A surprise?
I'm sorry that I didn't trust you!
It wasn't easy getting tickets, you know.
I'm really sorry.
Thanks, Mina!
Neku! The Noise has stopped appearing!
Yeah!
Those're the only ones left!
Run!
We did it!
Yeah.
—Let me treat you to something.
—And it looks like those two managed to make up. —Let me treat you to something.
—And it looks like those two managed to make up. —For real? I want a parfait, then.
You got it!
What a pain.
No, it's not.
—Friends help each other when they're sad or in trouble, and...
—Eri, what're you doing later? —Friends can help each other when they're sad or in trouble, and...
I haven't decided.
L-Let's go that way, Neku.
Wha—?
Hey! Hey, what's gotten into you?
—You haven't mentioned that girl lately.
—Nothing. Just hurry. —You haven't mentioned that girl lately.
Oh, you mean Shiki.
She looks just like you!
It's... kind of complicated.
If something's on your mind, I'll listen.
I-It's because... in here...
...I'm Eri.
Day five already, huh?
Hey, you okay?
Sorry.
I might not be much help today.
Why not? What's wrong—?
"Dominate the Scramble Crossing view at 3:00."
"Dominate the view"?
Three hours from now?
No matter how you look at it, that's just not enough time!
Come on, Makoto. I know you'll make it work.
We're playing the ad here at 3:00 p.m. It's set in stone.
Set things up so everyone's eyes are locked on it for me, okay?
B-But if we just play the video, everyone will walk right by it.
Hey, could that be today's mission?
Hey.
Oh, sorry.
I was spacing out.
Because of that girl we passed by?
Yeah.
That was Eri. The one I told you about.
She's cute, and smart, and everyone likes her.
I... wished I could be her.
That makes no sense to me.
Didn't you say you wanted to cheer people up with the clothes you made?
I...
Shiki.
I think you're fine just the way you are.
Let's clear this mission.
Yeah.
But how exactly are we gonna clear this mission?
We use Eiji Oji.
Everyone will listen if it comes from his mouth.
This water's totes delicious.
The Prince knows his stuff!
—That's that water from yesterday, right?
—It's just water, right? —That's that water from yesterday, right?
—I only got it because you waited in line for me, Sota.
—Yup. We might learn something about Oji if we scan them. —I only got it because you waited in line for me, Sota.
—Yup. We might learn something about Oji if we scan them. —I'm like, super happy now.
R-Really?
Thanks, Sota.
Looks like Oji's holding an event at AMX later.
We're giving out all of these?
You got it.
The higher ups are pressuring me to spread 'em around.
That aside...
...these things look like red skulls.
Damn!
Why's there another wall here?!
"Center St." Why's there another wall here?!
We're already short on time!
I wonder what we have to do to open it.
There's no Noise around, either.
Huh? What?
The requirements have been met.
Wall clear.
The wall's gone.
Go on. Take care of that pin.
Huh?
What was that about?
He told me to "take care of that pin," right?
There was light coming out of my pocket just now.
What pins do I have that you don't?
Probably that pin you got from that Reaper in the band.
Oh, that one!
Still, 777 is a Reaper, right?
I wonder if that means some Reapers are good guys.
Huh?
Why've you got two Player pins, Neku?
Player Pins are supposed to be one per person.
How should I know? I don't even know why I'm playing this game.
Oh, umm...
Having two might come in handy!
Like, if you put the spare pin in your chest pocket , it might stop a bullet, or something!
Seems like you're back to normal.
Huh? What?
Hey, Neku, what do you mean?
Thank you for today!
Last night,
I was lost in thought, drinking this delicious water,
when it hit me.
Red Skull pins!
What would happen if you all put these on, I wonder?
We made it.
Why, it'd be the birth of a new trend!
—Come on, everybody! Let's start a trend together!
—Okay. —Come on, everybody! Let's start a trend together!
I'll use Imprinting.
Watch the giant screen on Q Front  at 3 p.m.
Oh yeah!
I want you all to put on the Red Skull pins,
and then go watch the giant screen at Q Front at 3 p.m.!
It'll be our little date.
Please watch the giant screen at Scramble Crossing  at 3 p.m. today!
Huh?
The crowd's started to grow.
Looks like it worked.
I hope so.
Oh! Makoto!
Huh? Ai?
—Hi there. —Those girls are...
I'm really sorry. She found out about the surprise, and...
Good for them.
Two birds with one stone again.
You might be right.
It's 3 p.m.
What's going on?!
Look at that!
What's that thing?
Is that a Noise?
Hey, no one warned me about that thing!
That wasn't enough to clear the mission?!
There's no use.
We're done for.
What...
...just happened?
Looks like we cleared the mission.
So... we're safe for now?
That was different from the usual.
Yeah.
A lot of other Players got erased too.
One wrong move, and we'd have joined them.
You've been saving my neck all day, Neku.
I need to get it together.
I think you're doing more than enough.
You saved that part-timer from back then,
and stopped those schoolgirls fighting yesterday—
we've made it here because you didn't abandon anyone.
Plus...
...you didn't give up on me, even after what I did.
Lots of people have been saved 'cause of something that you did.
So, you're pretty...
...incredible.
Thanks, Neku.
In such a short time, you've changed quite a lot.
Have I?
I just...
...never want to screw up like that again.
Don't worry.
I know you'll be fine, Neku.
You seem down today, Eri. You okay?
Yeah.
Sorry. I know we're here to have fun.
So you do have something on your mind. Talk to me.
Okay.
You see,
—I'm thinking of giving up designing completely.
—Hey! —I'm thinking of giving up designing completely.
What?!
Why?! You're so good at it!
Eri, why?
If you wanna know, just scan her.
There's no way I could ever do something like that.
—I loved the outfit you showed me the other day.
—I'd feel like I'd be intruding on my friend's thoughts. —I loved the outfit you showed me the other day.
—I'd feel like I'd be intruding on my friend's thoughts. —I want to see more of your designs.
—It's not like she'll know. —I want to see more of your designs.
—Thanks. —You're overcomplicating things.
No, I'm not!
The thought of finding out what Eri really thought of me...
...scares me.
Didn't you say your dream was to be a fashion designer?
I can't do it without Shiki.
Shiki's incredible.
She turns the smallest ideas into complete items.
She's skilled, considerate, and a hard worker.
I think she had more talent than me.
But I couldn't find the right way to tell her.
I really hurt her.
You see, Shiki was worrying that she wasn't good at designing clothes.
"You don't have to be a designer", was what I wanted to tell her.
But what came out was: "You're not meant to be a designer."
"You're a great seamstress, anyways."
I wanted to apologise right away.
I was going to say sorry first thing the next morning.
But now...
...I can never see her again.
The clothes I design only become real when Shiki makes them for me.
So...
...I can't do it without Shiki.
That's... how she thought of me?
It was our dream
to make lots of people happy with the clothes we made together,
but now...
Even now... it still is our dream.
Neku, I'm sure now.
I want to come back to life and make clothes with Eri.
Excuse me? "Come back to life"?
Oh, right.
You don't remember that either.
This is the Reapers' Game.
My entry fee was my appearance.
I don't really look like I do now.
This is how Eri looks.
What do you mean?
The Reapers' Game is about testing Players to see who deserves a second chance at life.
I died in an accident.
Then I'm...
I'm...
...dead?!
Next time: "Erased."