My second game's started.
This is just the beginning.
We'll win and come back to life.
When we come back to life,
I want all of us to meet up again.
You can recognise me by Mr. Mew.
Okay.
Sorry for making you wait!
Shiki—
Shopping for clothes, right? Where to?
Wanna go to MODI or Parco?
How about Tokyu Hands?
Sure! Let's go.
That's what Shiki should've been doing.
But I...
Neku...
If I survive these seven days,
Shiki will come back.
A mission?
Listen up, Players!
What?!
You're all pawns!
Do what I tell you!
Game one:
Calculate the square root of 10,816
and seek out the solution!
Time limit = 60 minutes!
I'll spare only the ones who show up!
Incompletes will be destroyed!
Destroyed! Destroyed!
This is completely different from last time.
We defeated Higashizawa, so...
This guy's the new Game Master?
These are nothing!
I can't use psychs?!
Struggling with your second game?
All right,
I'll be your partner.
I can fight!
I knew you could do it, Neku.
I've been watching you for a long time.
The way you fought was wonderful.
You were watching?
I don't even know you.
I'm Kiryu Yoshiya.
Please, call me Joshua.
Was he a Player in the last game?
No. He wasn't one of the survivors.
No need to leer at me like that.
It's day one, so let's take it easy.
Hey!
Enjoy every moment.
What the hell was that?
Did I just scan him?
What's wrong?
No, Players shouldn't be
able to scan each other.
How concerning. You've gotta escort me properly, y'know?
You'll never win if you
don't trust your partner.
I can't trust this guy yet.
But the mission's already started.
I'll team up with you.
I think we'll make a great team.
Now, let's get going to 104.
What for?
You couldn't solve the mission?
The square root of 10,816 is 104.
Meaning that's where we should go.
Come on.
Has the game ever run two
weeks in a row before?
Yeah, once. But that was a long time ago.
You didn't know, Uzuki? Guess you're still a rookie.
"Rookie"? This is my second year.
How long have you been a Reaper?
Don't sweat the small stuff.
For now, it seems like all we've
got to do is stand around.
This is why I hate working under that guy.
I can't score any points like this.
I bet he's got some crazy plan that'd
go right over our ordinary heads.
After all, only a genius could've
made that incomprehensible thing.
What the heck is this?
Isn't this what they call "guerilla art"?
Wh-What the...?!
This junk wasn't here before.
Hey, there's someone on top.
Zetta slow!
You're all zetta slow!
How long did it take you to crack
that code, you hectopascals?!
H-Hecto... what?
I suspect that this means we've cleared the mission.
Oh, you're right.
I'm Minamimoto Sho,
this game's Game Master!
Putting in an appearance on day one?
How unconventional of you.
Convention is trash!
Crush!
On the scrap heap it goes!
Hmm?
You're a Player this time?
You recognise me?
A happy miscalculation.
This brings me one iteration
closer to my desired solution.
"Solution"?
What do you mean?
The games I design require
flawless calculations...
...and beauty!
I see the rumors were true.
Some Old Horses Can Always
Hear Their Owner Approach.
Listen up!
The amount orf weight I'm gonna
let you Players carry in the UG...
...is one yoctogram!
That'd be at the atomic level, I think?
Beats me.
No dice. This one won't open either.
So, Route 4 is open,
and 1 and 2 are sealed.
Routes 5 and 6 are sealed too, right?
Told you he's a genius. He works fast.
He didn't even let us know
which areas are open.
Doesn't he care about us
Reapers on the ground?
He gets under my skin.
What's the big deal?
Let's just sit back and watch
what the boss can do.
We should run! There's no way we can beat him!
Isn't getting here enough to clear it?!
Weren't you going to spare us?!
Wait, he's the boss?! No way...
It's over...
Hell no!
What do we have to do now?
Is there another mission?
I just wanna live again.
Those guys...
Don't tell me...
Attention, all you worthless yoctograms!
I want all of you...
...to die here!
Listen up! I just added a new mission!
Player vs. Player. To the death.
I'll save the winners.
Don't listen to that Reaper!
Trust your partners!
If you don't work together,
you'll get erased!
That was a close one.
Its weak point is its back.
Hear that?! We've gotta fight too!
Wh-What the hell are you—?!
I-I don't want to die.
S-Stop! Calm down!
That's the spirit!
Next,
I'll save whoever takes down that Reaper.
What?!
Come and...
...get it!
This is our chance.
Let's show them what we can do.
Come on, Neku.
Try asking first.
This work for you?
What is this power?
It looks like we really
do make a good team.
This will make all seven days a cakewalk.
As long as you and I keep up
our wonderful teamwork, that is.
I still barely know you.
But if you want to survive
past your second Reapers' Game,
you'll have to trust me, Neku.
It looks like this game
is gonna be zetta fun!
Don't you think so too?
Hi there. It's me.
We're in front of Hachiko again?
The whole area's sealed?
Hmm. I see.
Who's he talking to?
Then, if the wall on Route 3 opens,
I might be able to slip under
the guard in Miyashita Park.
Route 3? Miyashita Park?
That's fine.
Is he gonna swing by Cat Street?
Wait, I know these places!
I know Shibuya!
I remember this place and
all the connecting streets.
Until a little while ago, I didn't
even know I was in Shibuya.
So, why now?
Of course!
When you play the Reapers' Game,
they take the thing that is most
important to you. No exceptions.
Remember yesterday? When Rhyme said
she didn't have a dream?
I bet that her "dream" was what
was taken as her entry fee.
Kinda like how I can't remember anything.
It came back!
My entry fee from the first game!
My memories from when I was still alive!
Enjoy every moment.
To do that with all I've got,
I'll do what I want, how I want,
as much as I want.
That graffiti is from Udagawa!
I saw it when I scanned him.
And he's supposed to be a Player,
so why could I scan him?
Call me when it's ready. Later.
That's a menacing face. What's wrong?
None of your business.
Is this about your last partner? That was unfortunate.
Hey... just how much do you know?
It happens to all of us.
Every Player has something
dear to them on the line.
"Square root of 3."
"Root 3."
Do you know about this too?
About what?
Route 3. You mentioned it on the phone.
The Reapers refer to the streets
of Shibuya by numbers.
Route 1, Route 2, etc. in each area.
You sure know a lot.
I'll let you in on another secret.
This is a Reaper decal.
A Reaper what?
They're pasted on stores where
the Reapers allow us to shop.
Shop?
Hang on.
How'd you buy that?
I thought people in the
Realground couldn't see us.
Typically, yes.
Here.
We're made corporeal inside stores
with Reaper decals on them.
Why?
Who knows. It seems like Reapers
can become corporeal at will.
What a shame. The Route 2 wall is sealed.
That's where Skater-Brain...
Something wrong?
No, it's nothing.
Take us to Route 3.
This is Route 3.
It's the street that connects
MODI to Parco.
The countdown's still going.
Let's try walking around.
There's one of these here too?
Noise?
They seem different from the usual.
Piece of cake!
My attacks don't work?!
Thank you, Neku.
Let's do this together.
Fine.
Focus.
Sharpen your senses.
It's working!
One more!
Chew on this!
What was that black Noise just now?
It seemed as though we could only
damage it by attacking together.
Oh, was that it?
Don't tell me you didn't realize.
As your partner, that's concerning.
There weren't any like that before.
Yes. It's bizarre.
Taboo Noise, huh?
You say something?
Nothing at all.
It seems like that cleared the mission.
That girl.
She's Shiki's...
You always buy these.
My friend liked them.
I don't want her to be lonely,
so every day I go to visit—
I mean, leave offerings for her.
Oh, wait a moment.
I'm the one who's lonely.
Sorry.
It's my fault.
Shiki... I miss you.
Please, take this.
Huh?
I hid them in the back because
the flowers had finished blooming,
but they're still pretty, so take it.
Thank you so much.
Isn't that nice, Shiki?
She's skillful, considerate,
and a really hard worker.
But now...
Even now...
...it still is our dream.
So I'm gonna come back to life
and make clothes with her!
What about me...?
When did I die?
Where? How?
The memories I lost are coming back.
But... I don't remember my death.
Neku.
If you want to live,
you'd better listen to me.
I knew it! You do know something!
Why... am I lying there?
That's... Udagawa.
Blood?!
Is this my death?
Is Udagawa where...
...I died?
Neku?
Did you scan me, by any chance?
Beat?!
Hey...
...those wings!
You his new partner?
Yes, I am.
Well, whatevs.
I got orders straight from Kitaniji...
to wipe the floor with yo ass!
Pathetic!
You really think you'll last 'til
the end like that?!
Beat.
Shiki was taken as my entry fee.
So...
...I want to bring Shiki back to life!
You wanted Rhyme to...
I'll call it here for today.
Wait, Beat!
Beat!
Next time: "CAT."