"Man and woman in late teens left unconscious after a car crash."
So, Players in the Reapers' Game are dead?
And are then gathered to the Underground?
She's dead, and so am I.
And if we win, then we're given a second chance at life?
But then...
... how did I die?
Oh, Neku.
It's no use.
I still can't remember anything.
Your amnesia, it might have
something to do with your entry fee.
Entry fee?
When you play the Reapers' Game,
they take the thing that is most
important to you. No Exceptions.
She's so late. It's been 20 minutes already.
I wonder why she's late.
Right?
Remember yesterday? When Rhyme said she didn't have a dream?
Yeah, 'cause skater boy got mad at me.
I bet that her "dream" was what
was taken as her entry fee.
kinda like how I can't remember anything.
In my case, I didn't like myself,
so I don't get why they
took my appearance.
But now I know.
When I first realized that
I looked like Eri in the UG,
I was surprised, but happy.
I always wanted to look like someone else.
I thought that I could be like Eri,
cute and capable.
But... I just couldn't be like her.
I realised that it was still me inside.
I rejected that it was my issue,
so I envied Eri instead
and pretended like I was a victim.
But I did that to protect myself.
Now I realise that my individuality
is the most important thing to me.
That's why they took my
appearance as my entry fee.
But that doesn't matter since
I finally understand myself now.
Is that so?
If we survive all seven days, we'll get our entry fees back and, a second chance at life.
Two days left. Let's get this bread!
Yeah.
That said, I haven't seen
Beat and Rhyme for a while.
They've gotta be around here somewhere.
What will I do if I come back to life?
Thing's are going smoothly, I see.
Yes, sir!
Four Players remain.
I'll cook them all up
before tomorrow ends.
I'm expecting great things, Higashizawa.
I will not fail you.
When this game ends,
you'll officially be...
You have my most sincere gratitude.
Oh! Beat! Rhyme!
Over here!
No need ta shout. Ya gonna embarrass us.
Sorry about that.
It's fine. Only other Players
can hear us, remember?
Well... I guess so.
Whatevs. Only two days left.
Stay focused out there!
Yeah!
Whoa!
Oh, was jus' the mission.
You totally overreacted there.
"Reach Tower Records."
"No time limit"?
Huh? But that sounds so simple...
It's only a 10 minute walk away.
Aight!
Let's 'ave a race ta see who can
get there the fastest! Us vs. you guys!
Huh?
No problems, right? This way,
we can clear the mission faster.
I mean...
No cheating.
Let's move, Rhyme!
Ah! Wait up, Beat!
Here we go!
And that ain't cheating?
Hey, this is way too lax!
"No time limit"?! The hell?!
Are they making us work overtime?!
Yeah, yeah. Don't get your
panties in a bunch.
Oh! There they are!
Beat! Rhyme!
Slowpokes! Didn't I say this was a race?!
Are ya even tryin'?
The only one who wanted to race here was you.
Where's ya fighting spirit?!
Well, why didn't you clear the mission then?
What?
Tower Records is right there.
W-Well, about that...
Beat said that we should wait for you guys.
Wait, no! Come on,
didja really 'ave to tell 'em?
You're a softie, aren't you.
Don't you make this weird too!
I just wanted ta see Phones' salty face!
Wait up!
Think about it.
It's day six. The game's going smoothly.
The mission is simple.
What do you think the
Players are going to do?
They're going to let their guards down, right?
And then all we have to do is
follow the Boss' orders.
I guess you're right.
Im excited to see the result.
This way, Rhyme!
Huh?
That's...!
Rhyme!
Mr. Mew!
Shiki!
Rhyme?
Ugh.
And here I was, hoping it'd
get you all in one chomp too.
Reapers!
Rhyme...
Where's Rhyme?
Weren't you watching? She's been erased.
She bit the dust. Her soul is
now scattered across Shibuya.
You bastards did this, didn't you?
Well, who else could it be?
Cut the crap!
You... You erased Rhyme!
Oh no, I'm so scared.
The lil' shrimp protected you.
That is, until she was erased.
Shut up!
G-Give her back! Give back Rhyme!
I'd really love to deal with you myself,
but we're forbidden from attacking Players.
So all I can do is harass you with Noise.
We're gonna leave now. See ya later, skater boy.
Get back here!
Rules are rules.
Get back here.
Hey, let's focus on the Noise first!
It ate the other Noise?!
They're its prey!
It'll keep growing unless we
take out the small fry first.
This one's mine!
What?!
I'll avenge Rhyme by taking this Noise out!
Beat!
Put a sock in it.
You?!
From that time...
Name's Hanekoma.
Lemme go!
Ya won't be able to do shit to the Noise without a partner.
As if I give a damn.
A Player who loses their partner
only has a few minutes left to live.
I don't wanna be alive without Rhyme!
So you'd rather let your
partner's death be in vain?
Don't just give up.
I'll figure something out.
Beat...
Avenge Rhyme for me, I'm beggin' ya.
We'll handle it.
Roger.
Don't let us down.
Looks like things could get messy.
Let's start with taking out small fry.
Yeah.
I'll erase... every last one!
Just the big one left.
Yup.
Neku.
Not yet.
Focus.
Now!
Be Gone!
We did it, right?
Yeah.
Guess we're the last one's left, huh?
You're gonna come back to life
and make clothes with Eri, remember?
Yeah.
One day left.
Let's survive and win this,
no matter what it takes.
Today's the last day.
"Defeat the Game Master
at the Shuto Expressway."
And that'll be the end of the game?
Yeah.
Rhyme.
Beat.
We can't give up here.
A call?
It's me, Hanekoma.
Beat's gone.
What?!
Just end the game ASAP.
Once the game is over, the Reapers
will have no reason to erase Beat.
Got it.
This is day seven.
The Game Master, Higashizawa, is a daunting foe.
Don't die on me now!
Hane— Mr. Hanekoma, why are
you so concerned about us?
You'll know someday.
Neku, let's end this Reapers' Game.
Yeah.
Let's do everything we can.
Day seven is always so boring.
The last day is always the
Game Master's time to shine.
In other words, our job here is done.
Sigh. If only I could've erased those Players,
might've scored some extra points.
Thanks for waiting.
Two Mexican dogs.
Thanks.
It's always a pleasure eating here.
The pleasure is all mine.
Please, take your time.
You're too kind.
Hey!
Uzuki?! That one's mine!
I know.
Is this some kind of harassment?!
You...
Let's recharge our batteries for our next job.
Don't you dare take what someone treasures...
...and then sit around chatting,
you shitty Reapers!
What's up?
I was just thinking that...
I've experienced so much here.
Happiness. Sadness.
I've never felt so alive.
Even though I'm dead.
This is just the beginning.
We'll win and come back to life.
Neku.
Thanks for these past seven days.
I wouldn't have made it
this far without you.
We're not done yet.
You're right.
When we come back to life,
I want all of us to meet up again.
I'll think about it.
Great.
I probably won't look like this...
...so you can recognise me by Mr. Mew.
Right.
I'll find you.
Now I can finally start cooking.
We're not gonna lose!
What's this? Young lady,
that squid ink-like jealousy that was
brewing inside of you—what happened to it?
It's still inside of me,
but... I'm no longer ashamed of how I feel!
Of your dark, boiling
envy of your friend?
Yeah. My best friend Eri is so
amazing that I can't help but be jealous.
But she's waiting for me in the Realground!
So I'm gonna come back to life
and make clothes with her!
I see you've gone stale, young lady.
But a great chef like me...
...can make an excellent meal...
...out of any ingredients!
I'll take the lead!
Go!
What now?
Watch out!
Move!
Neku!
Shiki!
I'm fine!
We can't take another one of those.
Let's make this quick.
Yeah.
Let's go!
Right!
Got him!
Neku!
Mr. Mew!
My bad.
This is...
...the end!
To think that I... could lose.
Mr. Kitaniji... my sincere... apologies.
Is it over?
Yeah. We won.
Then, we get to come back to life.
It looks like we're being blessed.
Neku.
Where are we?
Are we alive again?
Not yet, I'm sorry to say.
Who're you?
A loyal servant of the Composer.
Kitaniji, Conductor of the Reapers' Game.
Congratulations on your victory.
First of all, this game
allows for the rebirth...
...of only one person.
What?!
Not all of the survivors get to come back?!
This is a rule set by the Composer.
It cannot be overturned.
The judges have chosen to revive...
...Shiki Misaki.
Me?
But why?!
We monitor every Players' growth.
You confronted yourself and
overcame your own weaknesses.
Thus, you were deemed the worthiest of rebirth.
Then Neku is the one that
should come back and not me!
Neku's changed in these seven days!
He pushed everyone away at first,
but he listened to my story.
He told me that I'm fine the way I am!
That made me so, so happy.
Shiki, you go back to life.
Huh? Why?
I want you to live instead!
If you are attached to the idea of rebirth,
you may enter the game again.
If you fancy the idea of destruction,
you can become a Reaper.
I won't become a Reaper.
I still don't know why I died.
I don't even really know if I
want to come back to life.
So, I'll enter
the Reapers' Game again.
Neku.
Don't cry, Shiki.
I...
Are you prepared?
Yeah.
Shiki?!
Shiki!
I can't touch her?!
Is this what you call "rebirth"?!
No. I've collected your second entry fee.
What?!
Neku Sakuraba, you desire to play
the Reapers' Game a second time.
You can't do that without an entry fee.
Don't tell me...
Exactly.
Your entry fee, the thing that
currently matters the most to you...
No way...
Neku.
...is Shiki Misaki.
Neku!
Stop.
Stop this!
Neku...
Shiki!
Stop!
Next time: "Reapers."