Beat...
Those wings!
I'll wipe the floor with you!
You're weak!
I want to bring Shiki back to life!
Hey.
How long are you going to mope?
Until we get a new mission.
It's a new day, but...
No sense waiting for what won't come.
What are you smiling for?
Come with me today.
There's somewhere I want to go.
You know the deal.
Each area of the Underground
is walled off.
So?
So, we can't go where we want.
I think the one by Tower Records is open.
Who knows when we'll get a mission.
Why not ignore it?
Someone else will finish it for us.
I have to win this game.
Your entry fee, the thing that
currently matters most to you...
...is Shiki Misaki.
I got Shiki into this mess.
To bring Shiki back to life,
I have to win this game, no matter what.
I have to do the missions myself.
Are you even listening?
I am.
Calm down.
It's here!
Reach Cat Street in 15 minutes?!
We've gotta run!
Hey! Where are you?!
Right here.
Let's run!
Did we... make it?
Run faster.
I hate getting tired out.
Neku, that's the place.
Huh?
Wildkat. That's where I wanted to go.
I recommend the coffee and pancakes.
And the donuts aren't bad.
That mission was...
A fake I sent you.
It worked even better than I imagined.
Be serious!
This is important.
For you too, Neku.
Mr. Hanekoma.
Hey there! I've been waiting, Joshua.
Mr. Hanekoma?!
Hey! You're playing the game again?!
So, the girl got to come back to life?
Shiki... became my entry fee.
It's my fault.
That so?
Don't cry over spilled milk.
Wait a sec.
You're friendly with Mr. Hanekoma, Neku.
Not really. He helped me out a bunch.
He's been helping me for a long time too.
How long?
You see, I could see things
that others can't.
Reapers, Noise, Players,
and even you, Neku.
Since when?
I forget.
Anyway, the Reapers' Game intrigued me.
There's one other person
like me in Shibuya.
Mr. Hanekoma?
Right. He helped Players that Reapers tricked
or tried to make self-destruct
using cowardly traps.
And once I started coming here,
things got more fun.
There're only dead people in
the Underground! How is that fun?
It is.
We risk our lives and desperately
race around Shibuya.
You won't find recreation this
stimulating in the Realground.
You volunteered for the Reapers' Game?
A place that never changes
might as well be dead.
I don't need that.
Maybe you don't, but I'm different.
I don't even know why I died.
I'll do what I want, how I want,
as much as I want.
I...
Here you go.
I'm proud of this coffee.
Thanks.
Hot!
Be careful.
Want a donut too? They're good.
No thanks.
More importantly, it's ready, right?
You bet. Give me your phones.
You too, Neku.
What do you need my phone for?
To add a new feature.
I asked for these before I
came to the Underground.
It's been a long wait.
Think of the guy who has to rush for you.
So, the person you've been calling...
Is Mr. Hanekoma.
Have I been too suspicious of this guy?
Hey, what were you talking about just now?
He said he saw the Underground from the
Realground and came here on purpose.
He comes to talk about that
stuff people won't understand.
My café's got Reaper approval,
so it's good for that kind of talk.
That's quite enough.
Well, you're partners. Try to get along.
Whoops, I messed that up.
Is it all right?
I'm supremely talented,
but messing with the Underground
from the Realground isn't easy.
Is it that hard?
I can't do my best work.
There.
I installed the apps you wanted.
Thank you. Now we can start searching.
Searching for what?
I'll tell you when we find it.
Seriously?
It's not worth getting
riled up at him every time.
Enjoy every moment with all you've got!
Those words!
What's up now?
Nothing.
CAT, someone I respect,
says the same thing.
You know the graffiti in Udagawa?
Yeah, it's famous.
That's some of CAT's best work.
CAT's multi-talented.
They can do anything.
Shibuya's full of CAT's designs.
You could say CAT's very existence is art.
Sounds like a big influence on you.
Anyhow,
the world ends with you.
If you want to enjoy life,
keep expanding your horizons.
This place is a melting pot of all
kinds of emotions, good and bad.
Things might be tough now, but hold
on to the last thing left inside you.
I bet it'll change you.
What if it changes parts
of him that it shouldn't?
I still believe in possibilities.
Any change on your end?
Not yet.
I'll just step outside.
You put it on my phone too?
That and a camera app.
You never know what missions
you'll get. Best to be prepared.
Oh yeah, we didn't get a mission today.
Yeah? Well, that's the Game Master's job.
This Minamimoto character
is unpredictable and cruel.
Watch out.
Neku, come here!
I got a hit!
A hit on what?
It's made to detect
high-energy signatures.
Is that what you're looking for?
I hope so.
I'm detecting them in Udagawa
and Scramble Crossing.
Udagawa's closer.
No, we'll hit Scramble Crossing first.
The size of this signature's a bit odd.
Red Skull pins.
It looks like everyone
here is wearing them.
Red Skull pins!
The signatures are moving
in sync with the pedestrians.
Is it picking up the Red Skull pins?
They sure are popular.
CAT's designs really are something.
They look like Player pins.
Player pins are designed and
controlled by the Composer.
The Composer? The Reapers' boss?
The Composer is above the Reapers.
They're capable of erasing this dimension.
Then... is CAT the Composer?
I wonder.
Was it the one in Udagawa?
What are you trying to do?
I want to properly guide Shibuya.
You'll come to want to help me.
Wha—?! Another went by?
Looks like it.
You  won't wait for a mission?
If we get one, it comes first.
Where to?
Udagawa. We missed it yesterday.
Now you're getting it.
I don't want to "get" anything. I just...
If I go there, I might
find out why I died.
Fourteen Players were confirmed
erased as of yesterday.
Minamimoto's not half bad.
This game might end before the final day.
But no missions have been
issued yesterday or today.
Then why are there fewer Players?
Where's Minamimoto?
Missing since yesterday,
but his "art" has been
sighted in various locations.
He's in the Underground?
Most likely.
He hates being part of a crowd.
Leave him be for a little while.
As you wish.
Any other issues?
Reapers across Shibuya have come
under attack from Taboo Noise.
So, that's what's erasing Players.
How does it affect our forces?
Not an issue.
I've already begun identifying
and locating the culprit.
I'm also investigating potential
links between incidents.
In that case, Konishi, it's in your hands.
Understood, sir.
Sho Minamimoto.
His numbers are second
only to Mr. Kitaniji's,
and he's easily the youngest
officer in Reaper history.
A true genius.
What on earth is he after?
The wall's closed.
Shall we look for an open one?
What?! Are you kidding me?
That's no ordinary mic!
It's Death March's heart and soul!
I'm telling you,
just report it to the cops.
No way! How would that look?
We're metal and Reapers.
But we've looked everywhere
and still can't find it.
We can use this.
What now?
We'll find that mic for you.
D-Don't just decide these things!
In exchange, we just want you
to open that wall for us.
Not a bad deal, wouldn't you say?
What do we do, Sota?!
There's nothing we can do!
We're in way over our heads!
What the hell?!
No one told me about a mission!
Taboo Noise?
Nao, let's run for it!
Don't let your guard down.
What are you talking about?
Noise don't attack Re—
You know, you're a real handful.
I can take care of myself!
And that was the last time I saw it.
You just forgot it.
I did not!
Maybe someone brought it
to the police as a lost item?
Not quite, it appears.
Look.
This mic's zetta sexy!
It'll make a perfect addition to my art!
Minamimoto took it?
And added it to that trash heap?
We can't risk touching it.
He'll kill us if we piss him off.
But you know who's responsible,
so will you let us through now?
F-Fine.
Isn't it great it came in handy so soon?
A camera that shoots the past?
Mr. Hanekoma's a bigger
deal than I thought.
Although I'm sad to say
it drains a lot of battery.
Two shots a day is the limit.
There's room for improve—
This is the strongest signature yet.
Hey!
You're Players, yeah?!
Huh? Yeah.
That place is bad news!
Better steer clear!
Bad how?
There's, like, a ton of weird,
black Noise, plus Reapers showed up.
We ran like hell!
I'm Sota. She's Nao.
Call me Nao-rin, 'K?
I'm Joshua. This is Neku.
Everybody else with us got wiped out.
Yeah?
Hey, don't go there, man!
It's pointless, yeah?
There's not even a mission.
Let's all win this thing
and come back to life!
Don't you know?
We don't all necessarily get to come back.
Hey.
What?
Your partner's also a rival.
So, like, if we win, and one
of us comes back to life,
what happens to the other one?
They just play again, like Neku here.
You've played before, Nekky?
Yeah.
So, your partner came back, yeah?
No, she didn't.
Because I decided to play,
she was taken as my entry fee.
Wha—?
For real?
In the end, it's my fault.
Sota.
Sorry, we've gotta go.
Don't overdo it!
What now?
What's with that Noise?!
Things must be bad if Reapers
are getting attacked.
They're fighting the big one.
Now's our chance to sneak through.
I doubt they'll make it that easy.
Take 'em down!
Below!
I won't make it!
You OK?!
Ow...
That's a risky way to fight, Neku.
Don't you want to win?
Yeah.
It's slow, but one hit and you're toast.
On the other hand,
it can't dodge ranged attacks.
It doesn't go down easy.
It's in a different weight class.
This calls for a joint attack.
Its attacks are powerful.
We can't afford to get hit at all.
Concentrate, Neku.
I'm through worrying.
If I want to win,
I've gotta trust my partner.
I'll erase them all!
Looks like Phones and Pretty Boy
managed to pull it off.
Like I care!
Anyway, we've got to report to Konishi.
I can't keep up with all
these irregular missions.
What a waste of effort.
That's some great graffiti.
Yeah, it's by CAT.
This is my favorite place.
And it's where I saw myself lying...
...when I scanned him.
What did he...?
What's wrong, Neku? You stopped moving.
Nothing much.
Just like back then.
Back then?
When do you mean?!
This is where I...
He... killed me.
Next time: "Turf."