Neku?
Are you all right?
I'm sure of it.
He murdered me.
Neku?
Are you not feeling well?
How can you look at me like that?
Did you remember something?
You need to work with your
partner to win the game.
If you want to save that girl Shiki...
You get the idea.
Damn it!
Until the Reapers' Game is over,
I'll protect you,
and I want you to help me.
What are you after?
I want to properly guide Shibuya.
You said that before.
Give me more details.
Do you remember who controls Shibuya?
The Composer?
Is you trying to meet the Composer?
There's a high-energy
signature down this alley.
And the Composer's there?
I think they might be.
You'll help me, won't you?
"Sir, I bear a rhyme excelling
in mystic force and magic spelling.
Celestial sprites elucidate..."
That's Minamimoto.
Quiet. He'll spot us.
Everything's ready.
Wh-What's going on?
It appears that my phone
was reacting to this thing.
What incredible energy.
A Taboo Noise Refinery.
Looks unfinished, though.
This is starting to smell fishy.
Another day passed?
Hello, Mr. Hanekoma?
It's me.
Two more days.
There's no mission again today.
Will we really be able to
clear the game at this rate?
We should be able to stop by.
He killed me.
I could never trust him.
But I have to win this game,
no matter what.
This is for Shiki.
I can't afford to lose.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Hey, I'm going to see Mr. Hanekoma.
You'll come with me, won't you?
Look.
I'm getting hits all over Shibuya.
There's no mission either.
Come on.
Fine.
It's closed.
I don't see a way around.
Our only option is to open the wall.
Open it? How would we...
Hey, that graffiti on the wall!
It's Noise!
Maybe the wall will open if we beat them.
I won't make it?
Found you!
Yo, Phones!
What?!
Neku?!
Stand up.
I'm gonna wipe the floor with you!
Beat, you...
Why are you doing this?
'Cause I'm a Reaper!
I don't want to fight you.
What? You wimping out? What a letdown!
Hey! What do you think you're doing?!
You've got to play by the rules.
We can only attack Players
directly on day seven.
And even then, only the
Game Master gets to!
I'm runnin' a special op for Kitaniji!
For Mr. Kitaniji?! Why would he pick you?!
Would you get lost?
You're in my way, old timer!
Come on, your phone's ringing.
Who is it?!
Hello?!
Oh, Ms. Konishi?!
Oh, yes. Right.
I'll get right on it.
Taboo Noise again?
Yup.
What a drag.
Well, let's go.
Hey, you!
Next time you mouth off to me,
you're dead! Got that?
Just try it.
Come on, rookie. Help us out here.
Hey, what the hell?!
Let go, damn it!
Bye. See you around.
Just you wait!
What is he after?
A pendant?
What is it?
This is...
...Rhyme's pendant.
He might have his reasons
for turning Reaper.
Neku, the wall is open, at least.
Let's hurry to Mr. Hanekoma's.
Mr. Hanekoma.
Oh, there you are.
Here. I need this fixed.
You sure did a number on it.
Hey.
Not coming in?
I'll... wait out here.
Oh, Nekky!
There you are again.
You're from...
Where's Josh-Josh?
He's in that café, Wildkat.
You'd better stick with your partner.
It looks like we're the only Players left.
I wanted some alone time.
I've been doing some thinking
about how your partner
got taken as your entry fee.
Yeah?
That just shows how much
you care about her, yeah?
Totally!
I'd be happy being Sota's entry fee
if it meant he got to come back.
And I'd play this game as
many times as it takes for Nao!
This whole time,
I've been wondering if Shiki blames me.
No way!
It's not like you did anything wrong.
Yeah! So, it's totally fine.
As long as everyone makes it back
in the end, it's no big deal!
Everyone? It's not that easy to...
No. You're right.
Thanks.
Don't beat yourself up about it!
Yeah.
You've gotta enjoy yourself.
Yeah. You said it, Nao.
Everyone, huh?
All kinds of people with all
kinds of issues live in Shibuya.
'Course, you're all I need, Nao.
Till next time.
Don't break it again.
Does he...
...have his reasons too?
I think that will depend on Neku.
What's that supposed to mean?
Is that store gone?
It was a cool place.
You know a lot about Shibuya, huh?
I grew up around here.
I walked around Shibuya after school.
With friends?
I didn't know anyone I liked talking with.
I thought so.
Those headphones are proof that you
don't want to get involved, right?
Where'd this come from?
You know, Neku,
you're closed off just
like the Underground.
You have walls between you and others.
The Underground is divided into areas.
The Shibuya Underground,
the Shinjuku Underground...
They each have their own rules.
You can't move between them.
Remind you of anyone?
I thought that my own
world was all I needed.
CAT's graffiti...
"Enjoy every moment with all you've got"?
It shocked me.
Do what you want, when you want,
as much as you want.
I wanted to do that,
but I'd given up on it.
I just had to act on
the values I believe in.
I felt like CAT told me that.
That's true.
You can't understand
other people's values.
You don't need to bother
communicating with everyone.
I wonder about that.
She— Shiki...
...had a fight with her friend
and never talked it out.
But when she heard how
her friend really felt,
she looked happy.
I didn't notice back then,
but Shiki's smile was so happy.
You've really changed, Neku.
It's fascinating.
New CAT graffiti!
Shibuya really is full of
CAT's work, isn't it?
I'm amazed he can find
the time to run a café.
CAT runs a café? Is it in Shibuya?
You've been there a few times now.
He's Mr. Hanekoma.
Who is?
CAT.
Huh?
CAT is Mr. Hanekoma.
Mr. Hanekoma is CAT?!
Are you serious?!
It's true.
Hey! Wait, hang on! Calm down!
For real?!
Mr. Hanekoma is CAT.
I always thought there was
something different about him.
Hang on, I've been talking with CAT?!
Whoa! That's crazy!
Is it that exciting?
Oh no! Did I say anything rude to him?!
No, scratch that.
I tried to tell CAT about CAT.
I...
I'm such an idiot!
Don't let him know I told you.
S-Sure.
OK!
Is today going to end without a mission?
It's a high-energy signature!
It's over toward...
I hope we manage to find it this time.
Hey, hang on.
You're planning to take on
the Composer, right?
Something like that.
In that case, I'm out.
I've got to win this game.
I don't want extra risks.
All right,
but I'd at least like
to check out the place.
I'll be satisfied with taking a look.
You can have your way after that.
You better mean it.
I won't get you any more involved.
If I can go two more
days without trouble...
Let's go check it out. But that's all.
Thank you.
It's just the other side of the
Shibuya Station Underpass.
Talk about creepy.
Hey, are you sure this is the right way?
I am.
It's in here.
We checked it out.
You'd better be satisfied.
I know. I'll keep my promise.
Either way, it appears there's a wall.
Sure it's not just dark?
It's a bit different from
the others we've seen.
I'll have to figure out how to remove it.
Does something feel off to you?
It's Noise.
What are those?
Black Noise, like the ones
outside Tokyu Hands.
Looks like normal attacks
really don't work.
Let's attack together.
On it.
Neku!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
I don't think we have
what it takes to win now.
If we can't win, we've gotta run!
No.
I don't think we can.
Not good.
Damn it! Is this it?
I've got no choice.
I was reluctant to do this, but...
What? Whoa.
You can do that?!
It really wears me out, so I'd rather not.
I saw that.
You're—
Sorry, this time I'm here
for pretty boy there.
I knew it.
You're not dead.
Huh? What do you—?
It was that move you used.
I've never seen power like
that in the Underground.
Players can't use anything like it.
Playing while alive is against the rules.
That said,
those Taboo Noise were a problem,
so I'll let it slide this time.
But next time we meet,
I'll erase you in no time flat.
Uzuki will, anyway.
See you.
The Noise are gone now, so let's go, Neku.
Wait.
You're... alive?
Was that Reaper telling the truth?
The cat's out of the bag.
That's right. I'm playing the
game while I'm still alive.
What the hell?
There are always loopholes.
Although, since I entered illegally,
I don't have a Player pin.
But don't worry.
I can make Partner Pacts,
so I'm the same as any other Player.
Like hell...
Like hell you are!
You're alive, but your just like us?!
That's a load of crap!
You chose to come to the Underground.
But the rest of us didn't!
We never asked to end up here!
We're not...
...playing this game for the fun of it!
You're playing to come back to life.
Isn't it a good deal?
It's your fault! You killed me!
And I'm saying, so what if I did?
Huh?
If I were the one who killed you,
Neku, what would you do to me?
Would you kill me, like when
you tried to kill Shiki?
How do you...?
I'm sure you weren't there.
I told you.
I've been watching you for a long time.
Since when?!
Why?! What for?!
Why me?!
That's because...
...this is your salvation too.
Taboo Noise Refineries?
A living Player is a big enough
problem on its own.
It looked like the Refineries
hadn't been used yet.
The Taboo Noise must be
coming from somewhere else.
You hear that another
Reaper got taken out?
In Dogenzaka, right?
They showed up by Tokyu Hands before that.
Nowhere's safe lately.
Minamimoto is making them attack Reapers?
I think it's possible.
Mr. Minamimoto was drawing
Taboo Noise Refineries,
so it's easy to suspect
he's behind everything.
Insufficient evidence.
A bunch of our people
have gotten taken out!
It was...
...my first time being attacked by
Noise since I became a Reaper.
I hate to admit it,
but I doubt I could have
survived on my own.
I'll make a report to
Mr. Kitaniji tomorrow.
You are to continue your investigation.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that going to be soon enough?
This is a zetta fun time!
I'll keep inverse calculating the world!
Two days till my solution!
Look forward to it, hectopascals!
Next time, "Joshua."