What's up, man?
Brain ware, main wave
Psycho got a high kick
Collect 'n select, 'n show you got best set
Crystals, blisters
It's all over now
Psycho cane, you're so keen
Need some more candy canes
Cold cake, cold break
Freak, you got a high kick
Mr. Twister
Moist with roistering
Stick it up, take it up
Step aside and see the world
Effect has defects
Take a bow to the moon
Morning rays, hairspray Queens
Get on their way to their nests to the west
Honest, they once had a dream
Belles of society, in the shells of their unity
Cornet 'n spinet
The sound flows, follows till they're home
Dragged by the powers of the dream
That power is yet unknown
Brain ware, main wave
Psycho got a high kick
Collect 'n select, 'n show you got best set
Crystals, blisters
It's all over now
Psycho cane, you're so keen
Need some more candy canes
Cold cake, cold break
Freak, you got a high kick
Mr. Twister
Moist with roistering
Stick it up, take it up
Step aside and see the world
Effect has defects
Take a bow to the moon
Morning rays, hairspray Queens
Get on their way to their nests to the west
Honest, they once had a dream
Belles of society, in the shells of their unity
Cornet 'n spinet
The sound flows, follows till they're home
Dragged by the powers of the dream
That power is yet unknown