Where... am I?
Pins? Where did these come from?
Oh, no. The light is gonna turn red!
What the hell just happened?
Scramble Crossing is always far too crowded.
Where's Hachiko?
Wait, what's Hachiko?
Oji Eiji was so totally cool.
What is going on?
Can they not see me?
Whoa!
What is happening?
I'm taking it.
Cheese!
What do you think?
Send it to me later.
I'm surrounded by all these weird walls.
I can't go anywhere.
I'm totally trapped.
How do I get out of here?
"Get to 104"?
The hell?
Numbers?
A person just... disappeared?!
What's going on?!
His hand!
Y-You're also—
Run!
Hey! What the hell is happening?!
Please.
Huh?
Make a pact with me!
What... are you going on about?
If we don't take out the Noise,
we'll be erased too!
Please! Just trust me!
F-Fine.
I'll do it.
What is... this light?
Our Partner Pact is complete.
Now we can fight back against the Noise!
See?
Hey, how'd you do that?
You should be able to do it too!
Just give it a shot!
Hell's that supposed to mean?
I refuse...
...to be erased!
Yeah! That's the spirit!
Phew! That was really close!
Take this!
The walls... are dissipating?
Wow!
You're a natural at using the psychs.
Psychs?
Yeah, like the flame power you just used.
That isn't the end of the Noise, so
I'm sure glad I partnered up with you.
I'm Misaki Shiki. But you can just call me Shiki.
Your hand...
It's a countdown to the mission deadline.
Just like on your hand.
But it goes away when
we clear the mission.
Umm, what's your name?
I'm... Neku.
Is that your first or last name?
Uhh...
You can't use your psychs without your partner.
That means we should team up!
We'll clear this mission when
we make it to the 104 building.
Why do we have to bother with that?
You saw someone get attacked
by the Noise and get erased, right?
We're all Players in the Reapers' Game.
We need to survive for seven days,
or else we'll be erased.
Partner Pact between Sakuraba Neku
and Misaki Shiki has been confirmed.
Man, what a pain in the ass.
Hey! Take this more seriously!
This is why you never get promotions!
Yeah, yeah.
You really get right down to hunting Players.
On the first day too, huh, Uzuki.
Of course I do. Unlike a certain slacker here,
I actually want to promoted.
Still, today's results kinda sucked.
That kid ain't half bad, is he?
Was someone watching me just now?
We've arrived at 104!
It was pretty uneventful on the way here.
Do you think this counts?
The timer's gone.
Yay, thank goodness!
Who's there?!
Honestly, I didn't think much of you,
but you're actually pretty capable, aren't you?
Black wings...
Are you two... Reapers?
That's right.
The more Players a Reaper erases,
the higher they rise in the ranks.
Huh? What did you just say?!
Do your best and entertain us.
What's going on?
Am I... going to be erased just like this?
I... I...
Where...?
Hey, you! You're finally awake?
Hwah?!
Whoa!
You startled me as well.
Where...?
We're back at Scramble Crossing.
Same place as yesterday.
Guess that means it's day two of the Reapers' Game.
I wonder where the walls will be today.
Hey. You.
It's Shiki.
Tell me everything you
know about this "game".
Did they not tell you anything
when you joined the game?
No. When I woke up,
I was lying in the middle of the crossing.
That's weird.
Well, this place is Shibuya,
but it's also not Shibuya.
It's like a parallel reality,
they call it the "Underground".
It's kinda like... the same place,
but only the Players are in a different reality.
The people we can see
are in the "Realground".
The pedestrians can't see or hear us.
However...
Here, try touching one of them.
Im so excited for 777's concert!
Did you hear it?
That's what Players call "scanning".
Scanning?
Yup.
We can't talk to or interact with
the people in the Realground,
but in exchange, we get the power to read their minds.
I don't like dealing with people.
So knowing what they think without
having to talk is fine by me.
Hey you!
Get your hands off me,
you damn Reaper!
Hey! Beat!
R-Reaper?
Who's this guy?
You ain't foolin' me!
You're totally one of 'em!
"One of 'em"?
Thats right!
I couldn't scan ya, so you gotta be a Reaper!
Hey, hey, wait a mo—
Stop with that, Beat!
Stay outta' this, Rhyme!
They're Players too, like us!
Eh?
See! Player pins!
Players can't scan other Player's minds.
You can't scan me either, right, Beat?
It's the same thing.
I'm Beat.
And this is my partner, Rhyme.
Nice to meet you.
My bad.
We got real screwed by this
pink-haired chick yesterday, and...
We know her!
Fo' real?! Y'all too, huh?
But thanks to Neku, we
managed to clear the mission.
Huh, so that means you're pretty tough then.
That guy always got his 'eadphones on?
Don't let that bother you!
I'm sure that he's just confused.
Oh, the mission's here.
"Set the cursed sculpture free.
Fail, and face erasure". Huh?
Here come the Noise.
Hey! Neku!
Yo!
Wait a second, Neku!
Neku!
Don't just friggin' run in on your own!
We should take them on together!
Shut it!
Sorry, but I don't want strangers
that I just met ordering me around!
Hey, maybe I should send out something beefier.
Don't go overboard now.
But this is nothing!
Mr. Hot-Headead over there
will self-destruct on his own soon.
Noise are attracted
to negative emotions.
Humans who get possessed by Noise
and negativity become loose cannons.
Shit!
This sound is really grating.
Why...?
Why do I...
...feel so irate?!
Damn.
We cleared it super quickly.
Neku! You okay?!
Ah, that was kinda boring.
Hey! You're that damn Reaper from the other day!
Are you sending us these missions?
What are you gonna do if I am, Sakuraba Neku?
Sakuraba... Neku?
That's my name?
Sakuraba Neku, let me propose a deal.
What?
Let's make a deal.
Kill Misaki Shiki,
and I'll free you from this game.
Huh? The hell did ya jus' say?!
Yo! Don't listen to that damn Reaper!
If you don't clear it,
you'll face erasure instead.
No, Neku! Don't let her get in your head!
I...
I'll do it...
Neku...
Neku...!
Please... don't kill me.
Ne...
Neku.
I will...
Yes! Just like that! Let that rage flow through you!
Alright, that's enough.
Stop.
The hell?
Are you alright?!
I'm alright.
What did I...?
Hey! You friggin' stupid, or what?!
Don't let your negative emotions control you.
The Noise will consume you
if you let them possess you.
Hey you, stay outta this.
It was just start to get good.
Ya gotta follow the rules, girlie.
Huh? Who do you think you are? My boss?
Who the hell are you, anyways?
The rules state that there
is only one mission a day.
and only the Game Master can send them.
Even then, the Game Master can
only start attacking Players on the seventh day.
Well aren't you quite
the knowledgeable one.
The Game Master is far
stronger than any Noise.
In order to survive all seven days,
you'll all have to work together.
And to survive, you must learn
to trust your partner.
Trust your partner...
Guess another day's gone by?
Shiki...!
...she's not here.
Of course she isn't.
Especially... after what I did yesterday.
Uwoah!
Ah, oops.
We ended up spooking each other again.
I got flustered because you weren't around.
I assumed that you'd be in the usual place, but...
Sorry.
What I almost did was horrible.
Wha?! I-It's fine! Honest!
Um, I mean, I guess you weren't
yourself in that situation or—
U-Umm...
Let's go talk elsewhere.
I keep saying we should team up,
but I never told you anything about myself.
And it's hard to trust a total stranger, right?
That's not it.
Huh?
It's because... I don't remember
anything about myself.
"Neku" is pretty much the only thing I can remember.
Until that Reaper said so yesterday,
I didn't know I was Sakuraba Neku.
You mean that...
you've lost your memories?
I see.
Mission's here.
"Vanquish the master of O-East"?
Ah, O-East is the name of a concert hall.
It's... somewhere in that direction.
I used to go to concerts a lot.
The most popular band
right now is Def Märch.
My friends love them and—
Damn, what a drag.
All he does everyday is yell at me.
I hope this shitty concert gets canceled!
Noise...
He's possesed, just like you were yesterday, Neku.
Sorry.
Huh?! That's not what I—!
Okay, for starters, let's take down that Noise!
Wait. That's not part of the mission, though.
Yeah, but we can't just leave him possessed.
Guess we've got no choice now.
Yea.
Wow! We were on fire just now!
It felt like we were totally in sync.
Really?
Excuse me, was I, like...
possessed by Noise just now?
Yup. A pretty mean one too.
Ugh! How did I let that happen?!
Thanks for freeing me.
No problem.
Hey, are you satisfied now?
We've gotta hurry to O-East.
Oh, you guys too?
Let's go together.
'Sup..
You're late!
I'm really sorry!
777! Def Märch's vocalist!
Oh, you know 'bout us?
Yes!
Glad to hear that.
Oh, these guys saved my life.
The Noise kinda got to me...
What? Damn you're hopeless.
In that case, I guess I gotta thank you.
Here. It's special limited concert merch.
Really?!
Yeah.
How valuable it ends up being
depends entirely on you.
Head on inside.
Thank you so much!
You seem pretty happy.
Of course! We got to help someone,
meet 777, and get inside!
Three birds with one stone!
Make sure you listen 'til the end.
The "master" should be somwhere in here.
We're running out of time.
Noise!
Hey, Neku!
Shit! There's too many!
Neku!
At this rate...
Don't try to do everything by yourself!
We're partners—
Behind you!
Is that O-East's master?
Huh?
Looks like ya strugglin' a 'lil bit.
Let's give 'em a show!
With the four of us together, we're stronger than ever!
Beat! Rhyme!
Get out of the way!
Yo! We'll take care of the small fry!
You guys handle that big one!
Hey!
What?!
Can we pull off that move again?
The one we used before.
We can if you trust me!
Alright, I'll try.
Okay!
Well then, let's go!
Yeah.
Neku!
Let's go!
Yeah!
Go!
We cleared it?
Neku!
Are you alright?!
Yeah.
Thanks, Neku.
I can stand up on my own.
Huh?
But...
...thanks for earlier.
You're welcome.
Yo! Y'all doin' okay?
Yup! We're fine!
Thank you so much.
It's just a bit of give-and-take, y'know?
Hey, I've got an idea!
Starting tomorrow,
let's do our missions together.
Oh! I'm down!
If Rhyme's keen, then so am I,
but what about Phones over there?
He couldn't help it before.
He was possessed by the Noise.
Plus, Neku can't remember anything
from before he got sent here.
He doesn't?
And that mysterious guy told us, remember?
To survive all seven days,
we'll need to work together.
Over half the Players in this Reapers'
Game have already been erased.
It's entered the final stages.
Yeah.
Let's just kill 'em all and get it over with already.
Minamimoto.
You're 9 minutes and 42 seconds late.
And you're as bitchy as always, Konishi.
Hm?
I see that wild animal has joined us.
Please refrain from such language.
You're being rude.
He's the current Game Master, Higashizawa.
I shall meet your expectations,
and prepare the ultimate
feast for you, Mr. Kitaniji.
Kiss-ass.
Don't disparage him.
He's a very capable worker.
Above all, he's far more
cooperative than you, Minamimoto.
"Cooperative", my ass!
I've recieved the Composer's permission
to promote you, Higashizawa.
I am honored and delighted.
There is, however,
one condition that you must satisfy.
Erase every single Player.
He was so cool!
"I'm gonna start a revolution
in the music world!"
How's that?
Oh!
Speaking of, how come
777 was able to see us?
Isn't it obvious?
Those guys...
...are Reapers.
Next time: "Shiki."